PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a creative and enthusiastic laboratory scientist (technician), Accountant and Web Developer with three years of experience in clinical laboratories, two years in accounting and one year in web development. I have an excellent experience in carrying out several laboratory diagnostic tests even with the latest updated technologies. I possess excellent analytical and communication skills and have dedicated approach to working in a highly controlled working environment. I am currently looking for a challenging opportunity within the laboratory, Accounting and Web development sector.

Meron Michael

Sig.

MERON MICHAEL ABRHA

Luanda, Angola

Tel - +244922706107

Email - merommichaelahw@gmail.com

Education

- Bachelor degree of clinical laboratory science, 2018
 Asmara college of healthsciences.
- Certificate of electronics and electrical maintenance, 2016

 Asmara international school
- Short accounting courses and tallyprime managments, 2022

 Luanda, Angola

• Self learned web developer from 2023 - now

Experience

• Hospital of Dekemhare

Laboratory technician 2018 - 2019

• Hospital of Adikeyh

Laboratory technician 2019 - 2021

Sebhat commercio Geral

Accountant and book keeper 2022 - now.

Web developer

on my way.

- Performed covid identification technics using proper PPEs.
- Utilized expertise in microbiology, chemistry and hematology to help with diagnosis of medicalissues.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- ➤ Offered friendly and efficient service to all customers, handled challenging situations with ease.
- ➤ Maintained and calibrated coulters, gene xperts, chem machines.
 - Perfomed accounting reports audits and consulting issues.

Skills

Technologically inclined

Excellent

❖ Online learning tools **very good**

❖ Online chat and emails **excellent**

❖ Product line knowledge **very good**

❖ Safety Guidelines excellent

❖ Online research good

Languages

✓ English excellent

✓ Tigrigna excellent

✓ Portuguess good

✓ Amharic good

✓ Arabic satisfactory

Accomplishments

• Finished **CLS** degree program with cumulative of **3.8** gpa.

• Scored **3.8** gpa in the Eritrean secondary school examination.

Interests

- I enjoy reading books, listening music, watching movies.
- I am a chess player.